When no one's out
Sneaking out late tapping on your window
We don't talk about it
They're invincible and she's just in the background
Wishing you never found out that love could be that strong
If our love is tragedy why are you my remedy
Lately I found myself thinking
Who gives a damn about the family you come from
That was as good as our song
I cannot find the way out of here
It doesn't matter what is out there
We don't talk about it
Our song is the way you laugh
Running around like a clown on purpose
Stoned in paradise shouldn't talk about it
Our song is the way you laugh
And I'm in the ground
Running around like a clown on purpose
Stoned in paradise shouldn't talk about it
If our love's insanity why are you my clarity
Running around like a clown on purpose
Our song is the way he laughs
And that's why he's spinning round in my head
We don't talk about it
If our love is tragedy why are you my remedy
As life breaks new ground
Sneaking out late tapping on his window
Who gives a damn about the family you come from
My head is spinning and I won't bail out
Our song is a slamming screen door
It cuts deep through our ground and makes us forget all common sense
Running around like a clown on purpose
If our love's insanity why are you my clarity
Shouldn't talk about it
As life breaks new ground
I'm finally looking around
If our love is tragedy why are you my remedy
Shouldn't talk about it
It cuts deep through our ground and makes us forget all common sense